<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Widas</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_">About_Activity</string>

    <string name="about_Text">As an innovative IT-consulting company
        WidasConcepts helps its customers to design business processes
        successfully. Whether big data, Internet of Things and mobile and web solutions
        - we provide modern and future-proof concepts and strategies. IT strategy consulting your divisions play
        across all platforms and devices optimally together. We take care of the business analysis and design modern
        user interfaces including the conception of software architecture and development. Internet of Things and Mobile
        Solutions devices and software solutions to support the customer in the background without being noticed at all.
        For a variety of concepts such as cloud architectures, Big Data and Mobility is the "Internet of Things" emerged.
        The communication with and knowledge of your / s customers, partners and employees will therefore be more and more
        in focus. For this, we create smart business solutions that take into account the context of the user, its mobility
        and local intelligence and inspire him with individual information, recommendations and forecasts. Big Data Consulting
        We offer the design and development of Big Data solutions from a single source. Let us analyze together your potential
        benefits and we will create with you an individual Big Data solution that will give you new insights and prospects for
        your business. Visit us: http://www.widas.de</string>

    <string name="aboutmore">Specialties
Big Data, Mobility, Social Platforms, sales and service solutions, Internet of Things, IT strategy
•	Website
http://www.widas.de/
•	Industry
Information Technology and Services
•	Grade
Privately Held
•	Headquarters
Maybachstraße 2 Wimsheim,Germany 71299 Germany
•	Company Size
11-50 employees
•	Founded
1997

</string>
    <string name="aboutdev">Developer- Amareshwar Bhat  amareshwarbhat@gmail.com</string>


    <string name="title_activity_gallary">GallaryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_flash__screen">WIDAS</string>

</resources>
